{
    "subject": "Raymond_Bernard",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Les_Mis\u00e9rables__1934_film_",
    "human_readable": "Raymond Bernard created the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.864859402179718,
            "question": "Who directed the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8552950620651245,
            "question": "What is the name of the 1934 film directed by Raymond Bernard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076246976852417,
            "question": "Who created the film Les Mis\u00e9rables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6481267809867859,
            "question": "When was the film Les Mis\u00e9rables made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6044906973838806,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Raymond Bernard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5960991978645325,
            "question": "What type of work did Raymond Bernard create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5293814539909363,
            "question": "What year was the film Les Mis\u00e9rables released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3886564373970032,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Raymond Bernard."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3415360450744629,
            "question": "Is Les Mis\u00e9rables a novel or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3292880952358246,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Les Mis\u00e9rables?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Raymond Bernard created the film Les Mis\u00e9rables (1934)",
            "html": "yago_12815_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Les Mis\u00e9rables a novel or a film?",
            "html": "yago_12815_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Raymond Bernard.",
            "html": "yago_12815_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Les Mis\u00e9rables released?",
            "html": "yago_12815_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12815_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Raymond Bernard being the director of the film \"Les Mis\u00e9rables\" in 1934, which aligns with the statement that he created the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}